Donatus.
ドナトゥス　ポスウェル
Poswell.
Linemile.
ラインマイル　ジャンニ
Johnny.
Colin.
コラン　トーニ　ウィラード
Tony.
Willard.
Ripley.
リプリー　メヒティルト　メイヨー
Mechthild.
Meiyou.
I'm sorry... I need to use you.
すまない　使わせてもらうよ
13 Years Ago
Why don't you just give them a pat?
撫でてあげればいいのに
They're your kids, aren't they?
自分の息子でしょ
I don't want them to become monsters like me.
化け物がうつったら困る
Geez, if it were something you could "catch" like a cold, I would have become one a long time ago.
もう そんなことでうつるんなら
私なんかとっくにうつってるわよ
I've witnessed many deaths since gaining this body.
この体になってから
たくさんの死を見てきた
But I was able to suppress the sadness by telling myself that death is just a speck in the grand scheme of things.
だがそれも　大きな世界の流れの中の一つと思えば
悲しみは少しで済んだ
Whenever I'd witness something beautiful or wondrous, I'd accept this body, thinking it'd give me time to see them all...
美しいもの　不思議なものと出会う度
この体を受け入れて生きていくのもいい
That's how it's always been for me.
ずっとそう思っていたんだ
Until I met you and had kids, Trisha.
トリシャ
君と出会って子供ができるまではね
I never age, but I'm watching
my kids age and grow like trees...
オレは年を取らないのに
オレの子供たちはみるみる年を取り　成長していく
I'm terrified all of a sudden.
急に恐ろしくなったよ
It reminds me that I truly am a monster.
オレは本当に化け物なんだなって
Dear!
あなた　あなた　ちょっと来て
Dear, come here for a second!
What is it?
なんだい
Good day, sir.
どうも　ご主人さん
A photographer?
写真屋
Try to look nice, now.
はい　ぴしっとして
We've never taken a family portrait before, have we?
まだみんなで写真撮ってなかったでしょ
But this is so sudden...
そんな急に
Hold on to Ed.
はい　エドだっこして
Okay...
We're ready now.
準備出来ました
Please take the picture.
お願いします
I don't like this...
参ったなぁ
Face this way, please.
はい　こっち向いて
Don't move, okay?
動かないでね
You know... someday, I'll turn into a wrinkled old woman who looks like a monster.
私だってね
いつか化け物みたいな
皺くちゃのばあちゃんになっちゃうわよ
But no matter how I end up looking, I'll always be happy to take a picture with the family where everyone is smiling.
でもね
どんな姿になっても
みんなで一緒に笑って写真を撮りたいの
So please... stay with your family.
だから　ずっと家族でいて
Don't distance yourself from us and leave us alone.
自分から距離を置いて　遠い存在になったりしないで
Don't hurt yourself by saying you're a monster.
化け物だなんて　そんな言葉で自分を傷つけないで
Okay! Say cheese!
はい　撮りますよ
Smile, Dear.
あなた　笑って
I was planning to accept this body and continue living like this.
このままずっとこの体を受け入れて
生きていくつもりだった
But I've changed my mind.
だが今は違う
I want to age and die with Trisha and the kids.
オレはトリシャと子供たちと一緒に
一緒に　老いて死にたい
That bastard...
あの野郎
That should do it...
これでよしっと
What were you doing up there?
何やってたの
Fixing the swing.
ブランコ整備
You're not really used to these things, are you?
慣れないことして
I couldn't do a single thing for them, so I wanted to at least do this.
あいつらに何もしてやれなかったから
これくらいはな
Trisha, I'm going.
トリシャ　オレ行くよ
Please wait for me.
待っていてくれ
Okay.
はい
Don't tell the kids about my body.
子供たちには　オレの体のことは言うな
Sure.
はい
Don't you want to say goodbye to them?
起こさなくていいの
If I see their faces, I'll...
顔見たら　オレ
You blockhead. It's okay if you cry.
バカね　泣いたっていいわよ
H-Hey, why are you two up so early?
あ　あら　どうしたの
こんな朝早くに
Al says he needs to go pee...
アルがおしっこって
Oh, so you were looking after Al.
そっか　アルの面倒見てくれたのね
Thank you, Ed.
ありがとう　エド
Just a bit longer.
もう少しだ
Can't focus. My body is still puzzled about what to do.
集中できてないな　まだ体が迷っているんだ
Shuuchuu dekitenaina mada karada ga mayotteirunda
I'm trembling. I can't stop even if I try to control myself.
震えていたんじゃ　コントロールしたってブレるんだ
Furueteitanja kontoroorushitatte burerunda
Although neither sun nor moon are on my side,
ツキ
太陽も勝負運もなんも完全にこっち向いていないが
Taiyou mo tsuki mo nanmo kanzen ni kocchi muiteinaiga
"I've no choice but to try,"
「やるしかないんだ」
Yarushikanainda
Those were the words I muttered to myself.
言い聞かせるようにそうつぶやいた
Iikikaseruyouni sotto tsubuyaita
The odds aren't on my side, but running way'd be gutless.
状況は悪いが　ただ逃げ出すんじゃ根性ないなぁ
Joukyou wa waruiga tada nigedasunja konjou nainaa
Even if I can't see the future, I'll just have to win it over with courage.
展望はないが　度胸でクリアするしかないや
Tenbou wa naiga dokyou de kuria suru shika naiya
Need to keep distance from the target as I hold myself back.
衝動は抑えたままターゲットとの間隔探れ
Shoudou wa osaetamama taagetto to no kankaku sagure
All that's needed for victory is pride to win.
必要なもんは勝つプライド
Hitsuyou na mon wa katsu puraido
Will we celebrate with the wine of victory
味わうのは勝利の美酒か
Ajiwau nowa shouri no bishu ka
Or'll we end up kissing their feet in defeat?
それとも敗北の苦汁か
Soretomo haiboku no kujuu ka
There are two outcomes to everything.
そう　すべては2つに1つ
Sou subete wa futatsu ni hitotsu
I want to control destiny.
操りたい運命の糸
Ayatsuritai unmei no ito
I need to seize the golden opportunity with my hands.
絶好のゴールデンタイム　この手で掴め
Zekkou no goorudentaimu kono te de tsukame
I'll finish it up with my best poker face,
渾身のポーカーフェイス　キメて仕掛けるよ
Konshin no pookaafeisu kimete shikakeruyo
And drag them into a world of illusions.
イリュージョンの世界へ引きずり込んで
Iryuujon no sekai e hikizurikonde
I'll find my way out of this endless pressure game,
際限無いプレッシャーゲーム　スルリと抜けて
Saigennai puresshaageemu sururito nukete
And leap over the borderline of honor.
栄光のボーダーライン　飛び越えるために
Eikou no boodaarain tobikoeru tameni
How many? What'll I need to sacrifice to make it happen?
ハウメニー？　どれくらいの代償がいる？
Haumenii? Dorekurai no daishou ga iru?
What is the one thing I don't want to let go?
手放したくないもんはどれ？
Tebanashitakunai mon wa dore?
Any luck?
どうだ
ダメです　やっぱりつながりません
No, I still can't reach them.
This isn't good... we can't contact the guys at base.
参ったな　上と連絡がつけられない
What now? Should we keep going?
どうします　進みますか
掘ったガレキを出すための出口が　どこかにあるはずだ
There should be an exit somewhere to toss the rubble that was dug out.
もう少し進んでみよう
Let's keep going for just a bit.
スミスは報告に戻れ
Smith, you go back to report on the situation.
Roger!
はっ
What's wrong?
どうした
Spread out!
散開
Are you interested in a perfect, immortal army?
完全な不死の軍団に興味はないか
He fell for it!
くらいついた
No death, no decay...
死なず　朽ちず　君も興味あるだろう
Aren't you interested?
I want to cut him to pieces!
ぶった斬ってしまいたい
It's just that the idea is so wild; I don't know how to respond.
いえ　突飛な話で
どう答えたらよいものか
There are only two choices:
You're either interested, or you're not.
興味があるかないか
答えは二択だ
I'm intrigued.
おもしろいですね
その不死が夢でなくなる日が来たら
So when that day comes, not just I,
but my men will also be able to benefit from this?
私だけでなく
我が兵たちも恩恵に預かれると
その日が来たらな
When that day comes, yes.
So he can't guarantee that much, huh...
それまでは保障してくれんということか
こいつらの話に乗れば
If I accept their offer, they'll force me to assist them in causing a bloodbath at Briggs.
このブリッグズでよからぬ事件を起こす
手伝いをさせられる
受け入れなければ代わりの駒とすげ替えられ
And if I decline, they'll put someone else in charge of the base, and I'll most likely be demoted or reassigned.
私はおそらく左遷
さて　どう答えるのがベストか
Now, I wonder what my best option is...
失礼
Pardon me.
どうした
What is it?
I'm sorry to bother you, ma'am!
失礼します　地下トンネル先遣隊がっと
The advance unit that went into the underground tunnel-
What about the underground tunnel?
地下トンネルがどうかしたかね
It's okay. Say it.
かまわん　言え
Roger.
はっ
先遣隊に異常ありと
Something has happened to them.
Understood. I'll be right there.
分かった　すぐ行く
I'll go, too.
私も行こう
All right, let's move.
よし　移動だ
Hang on!
ちょい待
こいつがいるだろ
We'll need to be tied up, right?
どうした　バッカニア
What's all this, Buccaneer?
はっ
I'm currently transferring the Elric Brothers from the east cells to the west cells, sir!
エルリック兄弟を東牢から西牢へ移送中であります
Who is that gentleman, if I may ask?
そちらの御仁は
Solf J. Kimblee.
ゾルフ·Ｊ·キンブリー氏
He's Lieutenant General Raven's guest.
レイブン中将の客人だ
Kimblee... So he's the Crimson Alchemist.
キンブリー
紅蓮の錬金術師
エルリック兄弟というと　鋼の錬金術師
The Elric Brothers... So you must be the Fullmetal Alchemist.
なるほど　ふたつ名どおりの姿
Now I see why you were given that name.
Oh... it's you.
あっ　こっちですか
It's been a while since anyone's made that mistake!
なんか久しぶりだな　このやりとり
Nice to meet you, Fullmetal Alchemist.
よろしく　鋼の錬金術師殿
どうも
Likewise.
閣下
General!
What happened?
何があった
We've lost contact with the platoon that went to investigate the tunnel.
トンネルの探査に入った部隊との連絡が途絶えました
And soon after, Smith's horse came back with an arm presumed to be his.
直後　スミスの馬と
彼のものと思われる　腕だけ帰って来ました
Just his arm?
腕だけ
What about his body?
体は
Missing, ma'am.
行方不明です
乗っていた馬は興奮しすぎていて
The horse he was on is too worked up
and can no longer be used.
使い物になりません
ヘンシェル　救援部隊を
Henshel, send in a rescue party imme-
This isn't good, Major General Armstrong.
これはいかんな　アームストロング少将
That hole is far too dangerous.
この穴は危険すぎる
What did you do with that biological weapon you were talking to me about?
例の不死身の生物兵器はどこへやった
Put him back into the tunnel and
cover up the hole, Major General.
元に戻して入り口をふさげ　少将
But our men are still-
中にまだ
I'm talking to the Major General.
少将に話をしている
Isn't that the law here?
ここの掟だろう
Obey the ones with power, Major General Armstrong.
強者に　力に従え
アームストロング少将
I'm Raven from Central.
セントラルのレイブンだ
大総統閣下から話は聞いているよ
I've heard everything from the Führer President.
Pleasure to meet you.
どうも
余計なことはしゃべっておらんようだな
It seems you've been keeping your mouths shut.
約束ですから
We promised, after all.
不服そうだね
You don't seem too happy.
Wouldn't it be strange to be happy after having people taken hostage?
人質まで取られて
不満じゃない方がおかしいでしょ
あの　いつ牢から出してもらえるんですか
Umm... when can we get out of here?
そちらの邪魔をしなければ
The deal was that we'd be able to continue
our journey as long as we didn't get in your way.
旅を続けてもいいって約束ですよ
そのうち出してやるから心配するな
Don't worry, I'll get you out of here soon.
地下の穴　あれもそちらさんの計画の一部でしょ
That hole... it's also a part of your plan, isn't it?
みんなにバレたら
If they find out...
You don't need to worry about that, either.
それも心配いらん
アームストロング少将は人造人間をトンネルに戻して
Major General Armstrong agreed to returning
the Homunculus in the tunnel and sealing the hole.
穴をふさぐそうだよ
The Major General joined forces with us, too.
少将も　こちら側の人間になった
閣下　行方不明の先遣隊の捜索は
General!
Aren't we going to search for the missing unit?
黙れ　ヘンシェル
Silence, Henshel.
まだ生きて　助けを求めてるかもしれないんですよ
But they may still be alive and need assistance!
黙れと言っている
I said, silence!
黙って従え
Shut up and obey.
力に従えねぇ
"Obey the ones with power", eh?
難攻不落のブリッグズの北壁も権力に屈しますか
So even the impregnable "Northern Wall of Briggs" has to give in to authority.
まあ　その方が賢いやり方です
Well, that's the smart approach to things.
ほう　あれが噂の
Oh? So that's the...
Good morning, Sloth.
おはよう　スロウス
よく眠れたかね
Did you sleep well?
誰
Who are you?
まだ眠い
I'm still sleepy...
おいおい　君にはまだ仕事がある
Hey, now. You still have some work to do.
プライドに言われているのだろう
Didn't Pride tell you so?
プライド
Pride?
面倒
It's a drag... but I have to do it...
だけど　しょうがない
めんどくせぇ
What a drag...
なんでめんどくさかったんだっけ
Why was it a drag again?
思い出すのもめんどくせぇ
Trying to remember is a pain...
心配はいらん
No need to worry.
こいつは中央軍のために仕事をしている合成獣だ
He's a chimera that's performing a task for the Central Army.
この国を更に強大にするために働いている
He's working to make this country stronger.
But it's still a top-secret mission.
とはいえ　まだ極秘の作戦だ
Now, cover up this hole, my friends at Briggs.
さあ　早くこの穴をふさいでくれ
ブリッグズの諸君よ
君たちは秘密を分け合った同志だ
You all are kindred spirits who I've shared my secrets with!
肝心なところが
The essential parts have been replaced with ancient Ishbalan, so I can't read it.
古代イシュヴァール語に置き換えられていて
読めないようになっている
I guess we can't help that, huh...
お手上げですか
If Scar were here, we might be able to figure it out.
スカーがいれば読めるかもしれない
イシュヴァールの僧なら
If he's an Ishbalan monk, there's a chance he'd know the ancient language.
古い言葉を知っている可能性があるからな
スカーさん　何かあったんでしょうか
I wonder if something happened to Mr. Scar?
見つけました
We've found her!
A little girl carrying a black and white cat!
白黒猫を連れた娘です
Okay, let's move.
よし　行くぞ
Mr. Scar! Sir Yoki!
スカーさん　ヨキさん
研究書はあったか
Did you find the research documents?
はい　確かに
Yes, we did!
場所を移る
Let's switch locations.
ここはブリッグズ兵に気づかれた
The soldiers from Briggs have already found this place.
急げ
Hurry.
A Few Days Later
This is fine.
これでよい
我々選ばれた者が神に近い体を授かり
We, the chosen ones, will be granted a body close to God's, and we'll rule this world.
この世界を統べるのだ
スミスとかいったか
Was his name Smith?
先遣隊についてはしかたがない
Nothing can be done about the advance unit.
選ばれた者のために　下の者は犠牲になると
So the weak should become victims for the chosen ones to survive?
That's right. Survival of the fittest.
そう　弱肉強食だ
弱き者が国の礎となり
The weak become the foundations of a nation, and the strong prosper above them.
強き者がその上に繁栄する
もしやイシュヴァールも
So Ishbal was also...
That's right.
そうだ　計画の一部だ
Ishbal was also a part of our plan.
そもそも弱き民は滅ぶ運命だったのだよ
Those weak people were destined to be destroyed.
そうですか
I see.
それは是非とも私に
Please leave that to me.
はい
Yes, sir.
お待たせしました
Sorry for the wait.
You certainly make a lot of phone calls, don't you?
随分とこまめに電話をしているじゃないか
レイブン中将はどこですか
Where is Lieutenant General Raven?
話しておくことが
I have something to tell him.
You were on the verge of death, but you somehow managed to make a recovery on the same day.
瀕死の重傷だった貴様が
その日のうちに全快してここに現れた
どんな魔法を使った
What kind of magic spell did you use?
Don't worry about it.
あなたには関係ないことです
And besides, you were jailed for killing officers. How did you manage to get out?
そもそも上官殺しで刑務所にいた貴様が
なぜ出所できた
I told you, don't worry about it.
だから言ってるでしょう　関係ないと
この計画はいつから
Since when has this plan been in motion?
I've heard it's been in motion since this country was created.
この国ができた時からと聞いている
And it'll finally be complete during my generation.
それを今私の代で完成させるのだ
ご協力感謝するよ　アームストロング少将
I thank you for your cooperation, Major General Armstrong.
I'll negotiate with the higher-ups and prepare a seat for you.
上に掛け合って君のイスを用意させよう
結構
No need.
What?
何
Was that Smith's left arm? Or his right?
スミスの腕は左でしたか　右でしたか
W-What are you...
なっ　何を
Aging is truly horrifying, isn't it, Lieutenant General Raven?
老いとは本当に恐ろしいものですね　レイブン中将
あなたも昔は本気でこの国を思う
I'm sure you used to be a young, dignified soldier who loved this country from the bottom of his heart.
若く　気高い軍人であったでしょうに
Y-You...
こっ　こんな　選ばれた人間になれるというのに
You have the chance to become a chosen one...
せっかくのイスを
I promised you a seat...
新たなイスなど不要
There's no need for another seat.
その腐りきった尻をのせている貴様の席を
I'll be taking the seat your rotten ass has been sitting on!
とっとと空けろ
You useless geezer!!!
老害がっ
Immortality... is right in front of you...
不老不死が目の前にあるのに
この地で文字どおり　国家の礎となられよ
You can lie there and literally become a foundation of this base, Lieutenant General Raven.
レイブン中将
I wanted... to become immortal...
私は　不老不死を
バッカニア　マイルズに連絡してやれ
Buccaneer, contact Miles.
はっ
Yes, ma'am!
皆はそのまま続けろ
Everyone else, continue working as if nothing's happened!
閣下
General.
Thanks.
コンクリ　きれいにならしておけよ
Smooth the concrete, got it?
へい
Roger.
随分つっかかるじゃないですか
You're being very pushy.
Is it because I'm a State Alchemist who served in the Ishbalan War?
私がイシュヴァール戦で活躍した
国家錬金術師だからですか
あなたどうすれば満足するんです
What can I do to satisfy you?
Do you want to know what kind of deaths your people experienced?
同族がどんな死に方をしたのか知りたいとでも
Shut up, Kimblee.
黙れ　キンブリー
お話しましょうか
Don't you want to know?
I told you to shut up!
黙れと言っている
少佐　よろしいですか
Do you have a moment, Major?
アームストロング少将から伝言です
I have a message from Major General Armstrong.
作戦完了　時間稼ぎはもういいだそうです
She says, "Mission complete.
You don't need to buy any more time."
了解だ
Roger.
やれやれ　やっとあれと会話しなくて済むか
Good grief.
Finally, I'm relieved from talking with that freak.
Even though I was putting on an act, it was exhausting.
演技とはいえしんどくてな
キンブリー
Kimblee.
レイブン中将の姿が見えないそうだ
Apparently, Lieutenant General Raven is missing.
どこか行きそうな所を知らないか
Do you happen to know where he'd be?
行方不明
Missing?
This isn't good.
参ったな
ここは素人が勝手に歩きまわれるほど
The base isn't built safely enough for people to just walk around.
安全な構造じゃない
中将に何かあったら
If something happens to the Lieutenant General-
それは有り難い
That's good for me.
I received permission from the Führer President to act independently if something happened to Lt. General Raven.
レイブン中将に何かあった場合
私個人の判断で自由に動いてよしと
大総統から許可をもらっているんですよ
ふもとまで車を出していただけますか
Could you drive me down to the base of the mountain, Major Miles?
マイルズ少佐
分かりますか
Do you understand?
My orders right now hold equal importance to those of the Führer President's.
今や私の行動は大総統の行動に等しいということです
お待ちください　閣下
Please wait, General!
完全に穴をふさぐ前に
Before you cover the hole completely, please send in a search squad for Smith and the unit...
スミスたちの捜索を
こんなこともあろうかと
The Fullmetal Alchemist created a secret passage in case a situation like this arose.
鋼のが　抜け穴を作っておいてくれた
She killed him?!
殺した　レイブン中将を
Lieutenant General Raven?!
Well, that's all I needed to tell you.
じゃ　確かに伝えたぜ
っておい
Hey! Wait!
When the hell are you guys going to let us out?!
オレたちいつになったらこっから出られるんだよ
Who knows? Ask the Major General.
さあな　少将に聞いてくれ
Dammit...
くっそ
焦ってもしょうがないよ　兄さん
Getting impatient won't do us any good, Brother.
今は　体を休ませた方が
It's more important to rest for now...
こんなにいろんなことが起こってんのに
I can't stay put when so many things are going on!
じっとしてらんねぇよ
やっ　どうも
Hey, how's it going?
鋼の錬金術師殿に面会をお願い
I've come to speak with the Fullmetal Alchemist-
おや　私なんだか嫌われてますかね
Oh? It seems as though I'm not very popular here.
今日はお二人にお客様をお連れしました
I've brought a guest today for you two.
A guest?
客
You idiot!!!
あほ
なんで来たんだよ
Why did you come here?!
なんでって　北国用機械鎧に付け替えるんでしょ
"Why"?!
To switch your automail to the kind they use up here, of course!
っていうか　なんで牢に入ってんの
Why are you guys in jail, anyway?!
誰も呼んでねぇだろ
No one called you out here!
What the heck is your problem?
何よそれ　心配してたんだからね
I was so worried about you!
軍の人が連絡してくれたからいいようなものの
I wouldn't have known if the people from the military hadn't told me about it!
The military?!
軍が
まあまあ　お二人とも
Come on, you two.
大総統閣下が大層心配していましたよ
The Führer President was very worried to hear of the situation.
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
巡り巡ってもまたここで逢いたい
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
はぐれないようにこの手をつなぐんだ
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
We used to talk all night until the sun rose,
朝日が昇るまで語り合ったね
Asahi ga noboru made katariattane
And held hands till the sun went under the horizon.
夕陽が沈むまでつないだ手
Yuuhi ga shizumu made tsunaida te
Let's walk together like this forever, like light and shadow.
こうやって明日も明後日も共に歩もう光と影
Kouyatte asu mo asatte mo tomo ni ayumou hikari to kage
I stand in the city, staring off into space with lonely eyes.
寂しげに見つめる街の中で
Samishige ni mitsumeru machi no naka de
I can't find warmth on my own.
温もりはひとりじゃ見つからなくて
Nukumori wa hitori ja mitsukaranakute
By meeting you, I realized
愛がこんなに強さになること
Ai ga konnani tsuyosa ni narukoto
How much strength love could give me.
知ったんだ　キミに出逢えてはじめて
Shittanda kimi ni deaete hajimete
Even if we part and meet again, I want to meet at this place.
巡り巡ってもまたここで逢いたい
Megurimeguttemo mata koko de aitai
Then we'll hold hands to ensure we'll never be separated again.
はぐれないようにこの手をつなぐんだ
Hagurenaiyouni kono te wo tsunagunda
I can't sleep by myself, 'cause I can't dream without you.
一人じゃ眠れない　夢は見れないから
Hitori ja nemurenai yume wa mirenaikara
So take me to a place where uncertainty can't reach us
どんな不安も届かないところへ
Donna fuan mo todokanai tokoro e
And let us bring light to the night sky with no stars.
星のない夜も照らし続けよう
Hoshi no yoru mo terashitsuzukeyou
So long as you're with me, I can go to world's end.
何処までも行けるキミとなら
Doko made mo yukeru kimi to nara
Even if it's a path I can't walk on my own,
一人じゃ歩けない道も二人なら
Hitori ja arukenai michi mo futari nara
If you're by my side, I can walk it while humming a tune.
鼻歌歌いながら歩けるんだ
Hanauta utainagara arukerunda
If we're together, the world is mine.
キミがいれば幸せ
Kimi ga ireba shiawase
キンブリー
Kimblee?
そっ
Yeah.
ブリッグズのふもとで看護師やってる友達に聞いたの
I heard from a friend who works as a nurse at the foot of Briggs.
大ケガで入院してたのに
He was hospitalized with serious injuries,
レイブン将軍が見舞いに来た後
but his wounds were healed right after Lieutenant General Raven came to visit, and he was released right away.
すぐに治って退院しちゃったんだって
レイブンとキンブリー
Raven and Kimblee...
That's about all the information I have for today.
今日の情報はそんなとこ
ありがとう　また何かあったら頼むよ
Thanks.
I'll ask for your help again when I need it.
またお店に寄ってね
Stop by at the shop again, okay?
振られたね　おにいさん
You were dumped, eh?
花でも買って追いかけたらどうだい
Why don't you buy some flowers and chase after her?
あきらめはいい方でね　遠慮しとくよ
I know when to give up.
I'll pass.
振る女もいれば拾う女もいるさ
There are women who will dump you, but there are also women who are looking for a match.
オリヴィエ·ミラ·アームストロング少将から伝言があるよ
I have a message from
Major General Olivier Mira Armstrong,
ロイ·マスタング大佐
Colonel Roy Mustang.
その花全部買わせてもらおうか
I'll be buying all of those flowers.
日本語字幕仕上げ：fayfay
手足を縛る鎖は意外な形をして現れる
The chain binding them appears in unusual form.
漫遊字幕組
http://popgo.net/bbs
少年よ　鎖をほどき引きちぎれ
Boy, unbind the chains and wrench them off.
手繰り寄せ　敵の正体を暴け
Reel it in and expose the enemy.
次回　鋼の錬金術師
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
第三十七話　始まりの人造人間
Episode 37, The First Homunculus.
策略と恫喝
Stratagems and blackmailing.
それは欲望への手段
Those are the measures taken to fulfill one's desires.